All right more features about the table saw.
Here is one of my favorite ones that is often times on jobs we will be doing work, we will have to take our materials we are working with and put them up and leave the saw unattended and we don't want to leave it where someone could walk up to it and come up and turn it on.
God forbid something happens to them.
This switch is the on and off switch.
If you notice I can pick it up and nothing is happening, that is because the key is not in.
This is the key.
Once you put the key in you are able to turn it on and off.
We don't have it connected to the power yet because we are showing you safety features.
A lot of times this is a good idea to use your shroud.
I think it is a great safety feature, these saws.